Guide to the Stevie Ray Vaughan Research Collection
The Wittliff Collections
Stevie Ray Vaughan Research Collection
1964-1995
The Wittliff Collections https://www.thewittliffcollections.txstate.edu
Crawford, Bill, 1955-; Patoski, Joe Nick, 1951-
SWWC.028
27 boxes
14 Linear Feet
Correspondence, printed material, financial documentation, interviews, photographic material, legal documentation, notes, creative works, audio and video recordings, and machine-readable records, created and maintained by Bill Crawford and Joe Nick Patoski, document the research, production, and promotion processes of their co-authored biography, Stevie-Ray Vaughan: Caught in the Crossfire.
Scope and Contents
Correspondence, printed material, financial documentation, interviews, photographic material, legal documentation, notes, creative works, audio and video recordings, and machine-readable records, created and maintained by Bill Crawford and Joe Nick Patoski, document the research, production, and promotion processes of their co-authored biography, Stevie-Ray Vaughan: Caught in the Crossfire.
The collection consists of three main series, the Crawford Files, the Patoski Files, and the Audio and Video Materials Series. The Crawford Files and Patoski Files represent each author's individual research, production, and promotion for the book. Generally, the series representing one author will contain material created and maintained only by that author, although some overlap does occur, as the two authors collaborated closely on this project. Each author's differing methods of research and production are revealed by the structure and contents of their files, which are listed briefly in the Series Summary, following the Series Descriptions. The Audio and Video Materials Series was created for ease of access to this varied material, which was created and maintained by both authors. It includes interviews, musical performances, a recording of Stevie Ray Vaughan's funeral service and consists of formats such as cassette audiotapes, VHS videotapes, and CD-ROM audio discs.
Because this biography of Stevie Ray Vaughan was unauthorized, the authors did not have the cooperation of the Vaughan family, including his brother, Jimmie Vaughan, nor that of certain other key figures in Vaughan's life, including Tommy Shannon, Chris Layton, and Reece Wynans, of his band, Double Trouble. However, published interviews with these important figures do appear in this collection, complementing the original research done by the authors. This collection sheds a unique light on Stevie Ray Vaughan's life and musical career. At the same time, it documents the rise of the blues in the Austin music scene during the 1970s and 1980s, a time when progressive country artists, such as Willie Nelson, reigned supreme. Of particular note are the many interviews with Stevie Ray Vaughan's musical mentors and colleagues such as Buddy Guy, B.B. King, W.C. Clark, Ray Benson, Kim Wilson, Angela Strehli, and Antone's owner, Clifford Antone. Interviews with Stevie Ray Vaughan's longtime friend, Dale Bramhall, twin brother to Doyle Bramhall, Vaughan's closest songwriting partner and friend, lend important insights into the history of certain albums and certain periods of the late musician's life. Many of the interviews conducted for this project bring to light what had for years been stories held only among Austin musical enclaves. Also, bootleg recordings of Stevie Ray Vaughan performances dating back as far as 1975, and many candid and publicity photographs dating back to the mid-1970s, are of special interest. Inclusive dates range from 1964- 1995, with the bulk of the material dating from 1990-1993.
A special note on interviews in this collection: Not all interviews on audiotape have written transcripts, and conversely, not all transcripts are represented by audiotapes. Existing transcripts are filed with the series of the author who conducted the interview. The interview audiotapes themselves are simply listed in alphabetical order in Series III, each tape has been assigned a number, and when a transcript is available for a particular tape, its location (by box and folder) will be noted on this list.
Conditions Governing Access
Collection is open for research.
Source of Acquisition
Gift of Bill Crawford and Joe Nick Patoski, 1993.
Biographical Notes
Bill Crawford and Joe Nick Patoski have been involved in writing and the music industry for most of their adult lives. From 1990 to 1993, they combined their literary talents and connections with the music industry insiders to write an unauthorized biography of blues guitar legend Stevie Ray Vaughan (1954-1990), who died in a helicopter accident near East Troy, Wisconsin. In spring 1993, Little, Brown & Co. published Crawford and Patoski's Stevie Ray Vaughan: Caught in the Crossfire. Michael Pietsch provided editorial assistance.
Born in New York City in 1955, Bill Crawford attended Andover and Harvard, where he majored in comparative religion. He moved to Texas after graduation and became involved in radio. He worked as a disc jockey at a music station in Midland and later earned a masters degree in business administration at the University of Texas at Austin. A freelance writer and radio and television producer since 1981, Crawford has produced segments for Music Television and the nationally syndicated public affairs program, Asian Communique. He was an associate editor of Third Coast magazine, and has written on media and business for Texas Business, Texas Monthly, and other publications. He was co-author of the book, Border Radio: Quacks, Yodelers, Pitchmen Psychics, and Other Amazing Broadcasters of the American Airwaves, published by Texas Monthly Press in 1987.
Joe Nick Patoski moved with his family to Fort Worth in 1953, at the age of two. He attended the University of Texas at El Paso, the University of Minnesota, and the University of Texas at Austin, where he began his career as a writer and consultant in the music business in 1972. Starting as a columnist with the Daily Texan, the newspaper of the University of Texas at Austin, Patoski soon earned a reputation as one of the most respected critics of pop culture in the Southwest. He worked as a stringer for Rolling Stone from 1974 to 1980, and as contributing editor for Texas Monthly from 1975 to 1980. During the early 1980s, Patoski was the manager and executive producer for several top Texas rock and roll bands, and toured the United States, Europe, and South America. In 1985, Patoski was named an associate editor at Texas Monthly. In October 1990, he wrote an article for Texas Monthly commemorating Stevie Ray Vaughan. Patoski has written on various other topics, covering the entire range of Texas cultures. His work has also appeared in Mother Jones, Village Voice, and Conde Nast Traveler, as well as numerous other publications.
Index Terms
Subjects
Blues musicians -- Biography; Music -- Texas; Blues (Music) -- Texas; Concerts
Subjects (Persons)
Vaughan, Stevie Ray; Crawford, Bill, 1955-; Patoski, Joe Nick, 1951-
- Bill Crawford Files, 1964-1995, undated
  Series Description
  Maintained by Bill Crawford, the Crawford Files constitute the bulk of the record group and reflect Crawford's original order. The records on the Research Materials subseries, 1994-1993, document the primary and secondary research of Stevie Ray Vaughan's life conducted largely by Bill Crawford. Included are a large quantity of interview transcripts and audiotapes, a copy of Stevie Ray Vaughan's death certificate, and Vaughan family genealogical material. Of special note are numerous published interview transcripts with the late musician himself. Material in the Book Production Material subseries documents the progress of the book's publication. Heavily edited manuscript drafts and page proofs comprise the majority of these records. This subseries also includes material relating to the selection of photographs to be used in the biography. There is almost no record in this series of public relations / advertising activities.
  - Research Materials, 1964-1992
    - Correspondence, 1981-1993
      - General (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - 2M correspondence, book contract with Little, Brown, & Co. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Financial and legal documentation, 1981-1986
      - Financial documentation (included performance commissions listed by date and locations played) (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Legal documentation (included blank performance contract rider for SRV and Double Trouble (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Interviews, 1991-1993, undated
      Sub-subseries Description
      This listing refers to interviews conducted by Bill Crawford for which written transcripts and/or notes have been made. Box and folder numbers in this list refer to these transcripts and/or notes. Tape numbers in this list refer to the audiocassette tapes listed more fully in Series III.)
      - Antone, Clifford, and Wilson, Kim Tape #1, May 2, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Bailey, Dr. Barry (pastor), December 18, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - Barr, Byron Tape #s 4-5, February 4, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Bernard, Martin Tape #13, October 29, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Bramhall, Dale Tape #16, January 28, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Bramhall, Ronnie Tapes #17-18, January 24, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Brandenberg, Cutter Tapes #19-23, November 21, 1991 - February 2, 1992, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - Brooks, Chris (with Stanley, Stephanie) Tape #100 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - Clark, Wesley Curly "W. C." Tape #30, January 8, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - Cook, Joe (including Vaughan family genealogical material, December 16, 1991 - January 6, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Daily, Gerald and Lois Tape #35, January 3, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - dePlique, Christian Charles "C.C." Tapes #39-41, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - Dishner, Joe Tape #42, September 26, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Dukes, Tony, and Pollack, Mark .) [see also Pollack solo interview] Tape #45, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - Freeman, Denny Tape #s 2/b, 54, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
      - Fullerton, Becky, Bramhall, Dale, and Fullerton, Tyrone Voss (Vaughan), January 12, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 19)
      - Greenwood, Mary Beth Tape #s 14/a, 60-61, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
      - Hatchett, Charlie, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
      - Hennig, Ray, April 23, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 22)
      - Howard, Steve (introduced by Margaret Moser) Tape #66/a, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
      - Kay, Pammy Tape #70, January 23, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - Klutz, J. W. (Jesse Wayne) "Sonny" Tapes #75-76, January 25, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Knight, Billy, January 26, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - Lingwall, Chris Tapes # 77/b, 79, November 21, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Lockett, Sandy, and White, Houston Tape #80, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Mario (of The Nightcaps) Tape #83, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - Markham, Jim, September 30, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Millikin, Chesley Tapes #84-86, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Owens, Terri Tapes #93-94, January 18, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Perez, Johnny Tape #12/b, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - Pollack, Mark [see also interview with Dukes, Tony, box 1/15], undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - Reno, Johnny Tape #98, September 22, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - Rogers, Jimmy (introduced by Margaret Moser) Tape #66, October 26, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - Stanley, Stephanie, and Brooks, Chris Tape #100, November 14, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - Steele, Mike, and K. F. Tapes #101-102, January 9, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - Stoval, Allen Tape #105, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
      - Strehli, Angela Tape #106-108, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
      - Stubblefield, C. B. Tape #109, October 24, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - Suggs, Michelle Tapes # 110, 11/a, November 30, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - Williams, Bill Tape #117, undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
      - Williams, Clyde Tape #111/b, November 22, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Vaughan, Jimmie and Stevie Ray interview with Ed Ward, undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Vaughan, Lenora Darlene "Lenny", July 21, 1992, undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Vaughan, Stevie Ray interviewed by Tarnow, David, Denberg, Jody, and others Tapes #123, 126, 127, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 24)
      - Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Notes (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - Handwritten notes re. unidentified interviews (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - Computer disk (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Notes, 1983-1992 (Box 3, Folder 1-4)
    - Printed Materials, 1978-1992
      This includes clippings from newspaper and magazines regarding Stevie Ray Vaughan's career.
      - 1974-1983 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - 1984-1989 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - 1990 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - 1991 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - 1992 (Box 3, Folder 9, Box 4, Folder 1)
      - 1993 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Personal (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Subject Files, 1964-1992
      - Alcoholics Anonymous / Vandenburg (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Austin Music (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Austin Scene (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Blues History (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Cocaine [including documents re Vaughan's 1979 arrest] (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Collins, Albert (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - Company Bios of Stevie Ray Vaughan (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Crash (including copy of National Transportation Safety Board report on crash) (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - DePlique, Christian Charles "C. C." (Box 4, Folder 13-14)
      - Divorce (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Guitar Magazine Articles (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Martin's Stuff (clippings re. Stevie Ray Vaughan and Jimmie Vaughan) (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Music Business (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Probate File (incl. copy of Stevie Ray Vaughan's death certificate) (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Soap Creek Saloon (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Southern Methodist University Program (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Smedley L.S.D. Bust (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Speed (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Stevie Ray Vaughan Articles (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Theoretical Stuff (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Tour Itineraries (Box 6, Folder 1-4)
      - Travel Notes (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Winter, Johnny (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Yearbooks (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Book Production Materials, 1976-1995
    - Book Proposal
      - Drafts (Box 6, Folder 8-9)
      - Correspondence (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Clippings (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Synopsis (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Bio Data (for Crawford and Patoski) (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Chapter Plans
      - Chapter Lists (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - Chapter Summaries (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Manuscript Drafts, 1992, undated
      - Quotes (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - Fact Checks (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - Table of Contents (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - All Chapters (Box 7, Folder 10-12)
      - Unnumbered Chapters (including handwritten notes) (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - Chapters 1-3, April 18, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Chapters 4-12, April 12, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Chapters 4-6, undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - Chapters 7-12, undated (Box 8, Folder 5-6)
      - Chapter 10 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - Chapter 13 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - Chapter 16-21 (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - Chapters 1-21, undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Chapters 22-32, undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Unnumbered chapters, undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Discography, undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Index, undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Little Brown's copy of manuscript (Box 9, Folder 6-8, Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence - Little Brown (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Page Proofs
      - Crawford copy of proofs (Box 10, Folder 3-4)
      - Little Brown's copy of proofs (Box 10, Folder 5-6)
    - Photographs
      - Permission to Publish Form (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Permission to Publish Forms - Complete (including correspondence re specific photocopied photographs) (Box 10, Folder 8, Box 11, Folder 1-2)
      - Photos Used (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Captions (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Photos sent by David Glessner (some used, some unused) (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Photos Unused (including early Stevie Ray Vaughan photos) (Box 11, Folder 7-8)
      - Correspondence re photos for Crawford/Patoski author bio notes (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Public Relations and Advertising
      - Correspondence (Box 11, Folder 10)
      - Excerpts Published (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Joe Nick Patoski Files, 1977-1993, undated
  The Patoski Files, maintained by Joe Nick Patoski, are divided into the same subseries as the Crawford Files: Research Materials, and Book Production Materials. The cataloger has maintained as much of Patoski's original order as possible for this material, but imposed some additional degree of order in the interest of accessibility. The Research Materials, 1977-1993, include numerous interview transcripts and audiotapes, published books on the music industry with Patoski's notes. Notable interviewees include Kim Wilson, Clifford Antone, Double Trouble manager Chesley Millikin, W.C. Clark, Angela Strehli, Stevie Ray Vaughan's ex-wife "Lenny" Vaughan, Marc Benno and Dale Bramhall. Please note that Patoski's groupings for "General" and "Stevie Ray Vaughan" in this series both deal with Stevie Ray Vaughan specifically, despite their differing titles. The Production Materials subseries, 1984-1993, includes manuscript drafts and page proofs, but is strongest in public relations / advertising material related to reviews and book signings.
  - Research Materials, 1977-1993, undated
    - Books
      - The Death and Resurrection Show: From Shaman to Superstar, Taylor, Rogan P. (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Oh Thank Heaven! The Story of the Southland Corporation, Liles, Allen. (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - Keep It Simple, Hazelden Foundation (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - The Hidden City: Oak Cliff, Texas, Minutaglio, Bill, and Williams, Holly. (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - Living Recovery, Hazelden Foundation (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - The Ultimate Guitar Book, Bacon, Tony (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - Charter Medical Corporation, Financial Prospectus, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Interview
      This listing refers to interviews conducted by Joe Nick Patoski for which written transcripts and/or notes have been made. Box and folder numbers in this list refer to these transcripts and/or notes. Tape numbers in this list refer to the audiocassette tapes listed more fully in Series III.
      - List of potential interviews (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - Benson, Ray Tapes #8-10, December 27, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Bentley, Bill Tapes #11, 12/a, February 3, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - Duckworth Tapes #43-44, February 13, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Ferguson, Keith Tapes #49-51, January 2, 1991, October 11, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Ferrari, Nick Tapes # 3/a, 52/a, 53/a, February 6, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Grandy, Phil Tape #58, December 28, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - Ham, Bill, January 29, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - Hodges, Alex Tapes #44/b, 64-65, February 13, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - Iglauer, Bruce Tape #67, January 3, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 10)
      - Johnson, Edi Tapes #68-69, November 10, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 11)
      - Kindred, Mike Tapes #72-73, undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
      - Luckett, Richard Tapes #81-82, October 13, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 13)
      - Nagel, undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
      - Newhouse, Jackie Tape #91, November 24, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 15)
      - Owens, Gary Tape #92, undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
      - Ratisseau, Shirley D., undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
      - Redbeard Tapes #96-97, December 11, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 18)
      - Rhodes, Joe Tape #52/b, undated (Box 13, Folder 19)
      - Richert, undated (Box 13, Folder 20)
      - Waldon, Freddie "Pharaoh", undated (Box 13, Folder 21)
      - Unidentified Tapes #118-119, undated (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Research Notes (Box 13, Folder 23-24, Box 14, Folder 1-3)
    - Stevie Ray Vaughan, 1978-1993, undated
      - Correspondence (Includes records of SRV's first session work with Marc Benno and the Nightcrawlers, 1973; also includes astrological chart created for SRV), 1973, undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - Photographic Material (Includes publicity shots, photocopies of snapshots of SRV and Double Trouble,facsimile copies of AP photos of SRV's funeral), 1973, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - Printed Material (Includes newspaper clippings and press releases, an unidentified short history of Oak Cliff, TX, and the book of sheet music and accompanying CD-ROM of SRV's guitar licks entitled "Stevie Ray Vaughan: An Exploration of Guitar Genius", by Marshall, Wolf. (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Subject Files - ARC Angels (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - Subject Files - Contacts for SRV book (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Subject Files - Discography (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - Subject Files - Drugs (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - Subject Files - Family Style (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - Subject Files - Funeral (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - Subject Files - Hammond, John (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - Subject Files - Jimmie Talks (after SRV's death) (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - Subject Files - Notes to be leads (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - Subject Files - Oak Cliff Quickies (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - Subject Files - Obituaries (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - Subject Files - Pictures/Sources (Box 15, Folder 13)
      - Subject Files - Sky Is Crying Reviews (Box 15, Folder 14)
      - Subject Files - SRV Manuscripts - General (Box 15, Folder 15)
      - Subject Files - Tape Info (Includes photocopies of cover art and liner notes, clippings) (Box 16, Folder 1-3)
      - Subject Files - Thunderbirds (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Subject Files - To Be Reviewed - Extras (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - Subject Files - Travel Notes (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Music Industry, 1977-1993, undated
      - Benno, Marc (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - DePlique, Charles Christian "C. C." (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - Printed materials (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - "Blues Guitar: The Men Who Made the Music" by Obrecht, Jas, Editor (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - "Burtons' Book of the Blues" by Wilson, Burton (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - "Crosstown Traffic" by Murray, Charles Sharr (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - "Hit Men" by Dannen, Fredric (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - "Love, Janis," by Joplin, Laura (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - "Musicians in Tune," by Boyd, Jenny (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - "Rhythm Oil," by Booth, Stanley (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Book Production Materials, 1977-1993, undated
    - General, 1991-1993, undated
      - Legal documentation (including contact with Little, Brown & Co.) (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - Financial documentation (including correspondence) (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Text and Editing, 1984-1993, undated
      - Little, Brown & Co. writing manual (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Drafts - Typewritten (Box 18, Folder 5-11)
      - Page proofs (Box 19, Folder 1-4)
      - Uncorrected advance proof (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - Computer disks (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Public Relations and Advertising, 1991-1993, undated
      - Correspondence - general (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence - serialization (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Cover Art (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - Ephemera (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - Financial documents (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - Interviews with Crawford and Patoski (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - Notes (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - Photographs of Crawford and Patoski (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - Reviews (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Audio and Video Material, 1975-1993, undated